Anton Zaharia

London, CR0 7AF | +44 736 711 1009 | zahariaanton95@gmail.com Github | Blog | Homepage | Linkedin

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

("There is no task shaped for Anton. Anton is task shaped!" CTO)

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming with a background in delivery services and restaurant management. Possess strong communication, decision-making, problem-solving skills and able to deliver great customer service, as well as excellent organizing and planning skills that enable adaptability, help to provide first-class service and meet deadlines.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MASTERED:

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL, Javascript, React, JQuery, Redux, JSX, ERB, HAML, Bootstrap, Bulma, CSS, SCSS, HTML, Google Cloud Functions, Cloudflare Workers, Web3

COMFORTABLE:

Python, AWS, Node.JS, React Native, Lua, Sinatra, Azure Cloud Functions, Webflow, Figma

Paypal, Stripe, Gooten, Zendesk, Slack, Facebook, Google, Twitter, GoDaddy, Cloudinary, Easy Project, Name.com, Syncfusion, (...)

Artificial Intelligence:

TensorFlow, ML5.js

More projects can be seen on antonzaharia.com

EXPERIENCE

Picfair London, UK Full Stack Software Engineer Apr 2021 - Present

- Working independently to complete agile tasks which include writing clean, maintainable and efficient code.
- Designing robust, scalable and secure features and contributing in all phases of the development lifecycle.
- Communicating with the design team to complete tasks and upgrading the website features.
- Integrating Ruby on Rails backend for the React frontend to facilitate further development.

Integrity Software Limited

Full Stack Web Developer - Part-time Contractor (Weekends) Full Stack Web Developer - Contractor

London, UK Apr 2021 - Present Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

- Communicating with the design team to complete tasks and upgrading different websites features.
- Developed, throughout the last 2-3 years, features and improvements for companies like: Nectain.com, proton-innovations.com, nash-fund.ru

Now-u

London, UK Dec 2020 - Dec 2021 Ruby on Rails Developer - Part-time Volunteer

- Working independently to complete agile tasks which include writing clean, maintainable and efficient code.
- Designing robust, scalable and secure features and contributing in all phases of the development lifecycle.

Hermes, Amazon, BCCP

- Created a program, and planned every 2 minutes of the shift to set an estimated time of arrival. Resulted in 97.5 % completion of deliveries, collections, and ETA daily.
- Adhering to assigned routes and following time schedules resulted in 100% routes completion.

Vype

On-site surveyor - Contractor

London, UK Sept 2016 - Sept 2017

- Traveling to circa 570 WHSmith UK stores, meeting all deadlines and performance requirements 100% completed.
- Communicating and working with 2-3 members of 5 different teams daily, resulting in a 5-star performance rating.

Papa Johns

Store Manager

London, UK Sept 2014 - Sept 2016

- Respond to customer complaints and concerns in a professional manner to achieve 12% sales growth.
- Delivered excellent customer satisfaction achieving top-performing franchise in London.

EDUCATION

SuperHiCrypto + Web 3 for Creatives course

London, UK Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Flatiron School

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript and React program

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Certified Web Developer, Javascript Beginner to Pro Certificate

Zenva Academy

Online, 2018

London, UK

Online, 2020

JavaScript Programming - Learn by Creating a Cross-Platform Game Learn HTML and CSS by Creating a Responsive Company Website

Theoretic College 'Mircea Eliade'

Galati, Romania

Baccalaureate Diploma, Diploma in Social Science

2014

HOBBIES

Parkour and Freerunning Video Editing Drones and Cameras

Youtube Video

Performed and Edited